[music]
I Was Once E.T. by Policeman. Oh My Papa
Hey.
Hey my father is a policeman, every policeman is mine
There is no father.
What kind of student was I in school?
Nudie Kid
The sporty kid [laughs] a teacher's pet. These
Teachers have stomachs. What would you do [laughs]
Brother? Brother, I think we should talk about the world.
It should be known that creepy men are everywhere
Is. Here it is. Identified himself. if you
If you were in our place, what would you have done? You
She is a reverse psychologist.
I don't know that much.
I went to the clinic today and she sat like this.
Was. [Laughter]
[Cheers]
Let's lock D. Not keeping my room tidy.
This guy laughed last time when we got torn apart.
Was. [Laughter]
The same thing that has been happening for the last half an hour.
fired
When will it happen?
Oho
[Cheers]
Don't Judge a Book Bites cover. But we thought
Let's try it. We are the judges in this show.
will introduce an unknown contestant to us
I will ask you seven personal questions about yourself.
And we have to guess the right answer.
The contestant has two lives. If we have two
Guess the correct answers to the questions and give them
Out. But if we fail, they can win.
Full ₹00.
[music]
Welcome to Drama Presents. Judge Me If You
Can.
[Cheers]
Hello hello guys, how are you?
Welcome to Dme presents H Me If You Can.
[Cheers]
A round of applause for our guest today.
Friends, friend.
[Appreciation]
Raunak has come specially from Mumbai for this.
Why especially brother?
I want Damesh's underwear. [Laughter]
Damesh Premier Innerwear.
Need premier innerwear.
Yes. Yours too Damesh has been a
Yes, yes, they have, they have, sponsors.
They have sponsored yes. Because Dominance
Friends, this is so great.
[Cheers]
They are the best, the most comfortable in a
Ware for Man. The Most Comfortable. As
There are no guarantees in relationships. like now
We are friends. I will fight like this
Will go. But their 30 day first trial
It is guaranteed.
How do I do it? Can you show that again?
Can you again?
I will do that with you. [Laughter]
And he will tell you more.
But welcome to the show guys.
Thank you so much. Have you guys seen the show?
Yes, off course.
Yes.
You have seen it. You are a veteran.
I have seen it twice, from here.
[Laughter]
Because I had to see it.
He is a veteran. You only came once
We had lost all the money. and once
If they did not let even one go, then your forest
The forest has been built. Today is the deciding
Decide. Best of three. Yes. Best of
Three.
A means no one will make a joke on this. Tall
I would like to claim it. [Laughter]
That today we will not get even a single question wrong.
Not even one today. One
100% yay or yay.
Or that's easy, friend. I Can Judge
Everybody Right Now. [laughter] They're not a
Contestant But You Can Judge Him. This is very
It's dirty. Very bad. I said that this
Ready to show that I don't know what
Is the show ready for? [Laughter]
It is very comfortable. I think he is
Wearing Dum and She Is.
Ok. You tell me generally that you are in judgment
How are you. I'm I'm Usually Wrong About
My judgment.
[Laughter]
Usually wrong?
Or how did you say that we are at zero?
only
But because he said that, I said that to my
You were also judged wrongly. [Laughter]
When he said this, I also became wide open again.
If or if this toy can clip too then I
Why don't I do it?
Ok. How are you brother, judgement?
Look brother, I am good at judging, but I
I couldn't put it into words properly
I find it. Like when I see someone
I do.
[Laughter]
I will do all this. So if my
He will probably tell me to choose an option.
I may not be able to do right or wrong, but even my expressions are safe.
Put the zoom camera on it
yes yes put it in zoom
Like if I say how are you feeling
you will speak
So we thought that this is not yes
Or if it's not A, then it's A [laughter].
So we kept guessing
Correct Correct
Tell me what you think for the correct answer.
You will say [laughter].
Ok so the correct answer is on Satmola, ok
and yes wrong for wrong answer
[Laughter]
Ok. Ok. Are we ready to start the
Show Now?
[Cheers]
The name of today's first contestant is
This is Lakshmi Sarbari. A
No no, there is nothing like that. Look at my friend
I was sitting next to Alia.
[Cheers]
Alia and Galia.
[Laughter]
Brother, that's why both of us are like T-shirts.
We did everything so that we don't feel left out.
or because use that treatment or
Well, Laxmi Sarabari, who is known for her
Sorry, I have a cough [laughs]. Edit
But it will be fine too brother, water and we will
pretending I don't know what happened
What
But brother, when can one be so comfortable without water?
It looks like
[Cheers]
Well, you know, if it had water in it.
Its absorbing capacity is amazing
Damage.
So, it means people have to stop wearing diapers now.
Have already done. They leave wearing damage directly.
Bus.
Yes that's what you've been doing?
Or [laughs] I mean, when this was going on, right?
There was a squelching sound.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Ok. I am calling you [laughs].
Come on Lakshmi.
[Laughter]
Our contestant today is Lakshmi Sarbari.
Known by her artist name, Sinkora.
They also call.
Sarwari is 26 years old and a housewife by profession.
Is a DJ and producer. About Sarvari
Let me know one thing in advance. this backup
Doesn't believe in plans.
Sorry Chirag. [sound of clearing throat]
[Laughter]
She Always Wanted to Create a Show That Mixes
Music and cooking together. What?
Ok. And whichever girl he had a crush on
She feels shy in front of him.
Ok.
And if Sharvari wins ₹00 today then she
We will buy speakers with that money.
Oh good for
Or motivational speakers. [Laughter]
Ok. Call Sarwari.
Yes.
Please bang. I welcome Lakshmi Sarwari.
I think I'm just gonna be myself. I
I'm gonna try and keep a poker face. I am
Not the Kind of Person That [Music] I Look
Like. So It Should Be Pretty Hard for Them
To figure me out. My Hair Is the Most
Misleading thing in my appearance because I
Think It Makes Me Look Very Bold [Music]
Which in some cases I am not. I am not
Really here for the money. I think I just
Here to have fun. So Hopefully We Can
Have some fun. The show is very fun. it's my
Kind of show. I like that then judge everyone
When Usually [Music] I'm the Person
Dudge. But I don't tell hit. So
Lakshmi Lakshmi [encouraging voice]
Lakshmi Lakshmi. what does sarbari mean
Is? Actress in Munjiya.
Oh [laughs]
It Means Twilight.
Twilight, oh brother [laughs].
What time does toilet light fall?
Okay all right. Why is it called Sean Fog?
Meaning it would have been difficult to pronounce Sarvari
It is for the people. So
I do remember the fog, right? So it means
Then say anything. then
Means intuition. Ok.
End
Okay all right. Now we have because of
There was a contest about it. What we give you
Call?
Sarvari.
Savary. That was tough, wasn't it?
Call Sinkora.
I will call Sinkora. Ok.
whatever you want
They call it Sinkora.
Sinkora
It seems like the name of some fan.
Right?
a little Sinkora
Its ad is coming in IPL.
Yes. Because we have no context
It is not about Sinkora. So I think
We should ask them two questions each. I will
Start with the Waitron here.
You are the house DJ. This means you are someone
You cannot play in a commercial place.
Are we judging you? [Laughter]
You Thought That She Is a House DJ Because
She doesn't play outside.
Because she married an operator who tells her
Don't go out of the house but DJ.
Whatever DJing you want to do, do it while staying inside the house.
[laughter] Do it. Because he wrote somewhere
I was also into music and cooking.
I live with both of them. So I thought something
There must be some pressure. You think that you
Let's be a little comedy sensitive at this time
Is it happening? [Laughter]
Do you think after such statements
An apology video comes. friends of mine
That means it absolutely
I have learned a lot from my mistake.
I will apologize to him in such a way that
I didn't want to speak. blessings to me
The chutes had to be cut from the side. [Laughter]
He was calling me by fingering me.
Some of my OK is fine. Then tell me.
Ok. Ok. So you wasted this question.
Is done. Thankfully. Tell me sir, Raunak
Rajwani.
What are the top three artists on your
Spotify Rap? Will we reach anywhere with that?
[Laughter]
No, I came here for music recommendations.
I.
You need songs for the return flight.
[Laughter]
It's Luke Lassie, Rodigo AM and this guy
Called Signy Charles.
Such a beloved is not a beloved.
I did not understand that. Tell us about this
Who knows?
The names of these people are also very difficult. V
Should call all of them Syncora.
[Laughter]
Bhai One Two Three
Before asking the second question, think about you once
I will confirm from. Only if you do it alone
I will ask.
Absolutely not allowed.
Okay [laughs].
I am asking you before this. not from them
I am asking. ok not your account
It will happen. Ye Rudrego AM Night Music
No.
[Appreciation]
Oh my God. So it happens at night only.
It plays only at night. Ok ok fine.
[laughter] Okay. ok my question is
What? ask a good question
This is a good question, isn't it allowed or not?
No [laughter] it is not.
Okay, my question is this: I
So I want to play it right [laughs].
What was your dream that you could not fulfill?
You get
I wanted to be an artist I wanted to
Start a Label with My Paintings on It
That I Didn't Do |
Label with your painting
Label in the sense like a clothing label
Clothing Labels
Or
Oh so you don't want anything in life, a stable job
don't want
You don't need regular incoming money. [Laughter]
Ok. Ok. Brother, this is an artist type person.
Is. Look, we got some gauge done from this. Now
What did we gauge from that? Are you in the house
If you are a DJ then
How do you live outside the house, sister? not that
found to be.
Right and he was going to get all
Judgements correct in the [laughter] first.
Even you.
That's all I was saying.
I was doing it in the square [laughs].
I was just talking openly, friend.
Let me try to ask the second sincerely.
Second question sincerely.
It's been a second, right? No no no that's not
No, actually I tell them this is
My Show
Hey [encouraging voice] you do that
You give it, then the reel comes, the badtameez comedian
I am joking, we did not allow seconds.
did his
Yes, I am oppressed, he has oppressed me.
No, I didn't [laughs].
He is a house comedian
[Appreciation]
yes brother go ahead
If you have to choose one Bollywood celebrity
You have to do whatever is of your closest interest.
in personality
So who will be the one with whom you will like the most?
Do you match personality wise?
Maybe Shahrukh Khan is like loyal.
Loyal
Loyal I field I think he stands by the
By His People.
Correct.
Yeah.
He stands by.
By All That.
Takes a lot of space.
But it does stand there.
It will stand in the way, right? [Laughter]
What's the problem?
Ok. Ok. Your question friend. or my
The question is who cheated on you
Gauri [laughs]
It's a question
Just Shekant answer there, ask again.
another question
Or
ok fine i have a generic question your
Swig [laughs]
Most Ordered
items items
or items
Most Ordered
Biryani and Shawarma
Biryani and shawarma, what should I do now [laughs]
Place two plates each.
[Appreciation]
So you have two questions. My question remains
Is. Firstly, we are a little more
So we speak in English. You have also come.
I stopped being able to understand.
In the Ilebro test pilot. actually
I thought I was a bit like you're the hobbyist type
She is a woman of. It looked dirty, man. so
I have consciously changed my hobby.
Had done it.
If you are a hobby type of woman then always don't
Speak.
Yes. So leave this phrase. Right
Right correct. [Laughter]
You know she is an artist. She Likes She
Likes Iborate Food. So that means she
He likes things that require effort. a little something
He worked on it. Those two English ones
He also likes three musicians.
Ok. [sound of clearing throat] mine
The question is what is your relationship?
With your parents? He is happy with you now
These careers are based on your current life or your choices.
Wali?
Oh wow judging already.
Near.
She is being rude. being very rude
Is.
Call home. [Laughter]
How can I say that she doesn't even listen to me.
Well, I have to ask another question.
How much debt do you have?
₹00 [laughs]
Is there nothing?
There is nothing on loan. Ok. from any of its
There is no conversation. There is no conversation. Bad
Not a human being. But she is a woman of colourful temperament.
[Laughter]
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
I will not only upload the video but also the entire
Only one video will be available, of 30 seconds.
I just said you are colorful
Finished video [laughs]
Okay, okay, let's start the main presentation.
That We Begin Guys
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Okay, first question on our screens.
Please for ₹2000
I once dated a woman who was
Turn straight after the breakup [laughs].
Corrected Grammar in Every Argument
Had a backup before breaking up with me
New My Passwords But Not My Birthday
Oh brother, whoever the lady from the fourth is, has come.
Respect her [laughs].
Okay, look, let me tell you all.
He gave only one answer out of these.
When the question was asked, the remaining options were given by our team.
have created to confuse us, so that
We have to think accordingly
Had a backup before breaking up with me, friend
I find this interesting bro
Because it seems very easy.
No, because he could have said this too.
And this may have been said by the team as well.
To confuse. Look because we
I also know that she is a loyal
Enthusiast. He is fond of loyalty.
Loyalty is fond of [laughs].
Because she is a hobbyist.
She is fond of hobbies.
Correct correct. Correct.
Let's eliminate one first. Look, look
Corrected grammar in every argument
Is not a story uniform girl. that the girl
She used to interrupt me. This thing is like this
I will not tell.
Such a fourth thing new my passwords but
Not even my birthday, not by flattering like this
He will tell that brother does not even tell his birthday
Actually, he can tell a little bit if he
You snoop, but she won't snoop.
Because this means loyalty snooping
Snoop Dogg
Or checking someone spawn without permission
But why is she putting in efforts etc. on these?
Which school teaches all this?
When they say that this is what you are doing
This is snooping, Chirag, stop telling everyone this.
[laughs]
ok well okay okay okay okay my
I think you should get one of A or C.
Let's takeit.
CeCe Turns Straight After Breakup Is I
Think it's a trick question. I think we
Are being made to answer that so that we are
Told that this cannot happen. You Can't Turn
Straight and then we'll go to jail.
So this is such a big trick.
or or
that these [laughter] people basically these people basically
Want another job.
So that's how good he applied somewhere.
He did it and got selected. Okay okay.
Ok. So this is their notice period. [Laughter]
I am feeling a little naive.
I will give you the explanation. If wrong
If you feel like it, please edit it from the show, brother.
Let's see brother.
Ok. this could be somebody
Tell me in Hindi.
Well, it could be someone who
Speak in English.
I speak one word in English and one in Hindi
I speak. Third Sanskrit [laughs]
Let's do this.
Marani
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
He might have dated someone
Those who are very early in life are not sure.
The by Curious The
And like you
Or [laughter]
By Curious
No no or we are not very content with them
Give
[Laughter]
Will they make that with AI?
Yes, I am also feeling the same.
And also it is a fun story that it will tell
To the people that this happened, this happened because I
did such a great job
Why did it become someone else's?
How alarm is ending good.
Hey, the music is that, it's house music.
[Laughter]
[Cheers]
I think we go a long way together
Don't waste time.
I think it's C.
C
No but see is too easy. Ok let's go. I think it's
B.
What?
Correct it grammar.
I think it's B. But if you guys say this
If you are staying then I will go. Then you guys are wrong
Will be.
Oh!
Or. I also think it's a only.
Come, let us support you and go to B.
No I think it's a. [Laughter]
Tell me what is your final result.
If you're if both of you're from o is.
Since both of you are saying.
Not like this.
I am also saying.
Take ownership.
If there is a case then who led it? [Laughter]
Ah, turn straight after a breakup. Ok,
OK, A. Ok. Lock A up, guys.
For ₹2,000. Hey, are the speakers coming?
Then will come what we call the lead.
[Laughter]
Look, the lead shines through it all. You are the first
You are telling me. Lead pe apna [laughs] guy. One
So people tell me this, brother, you are your
He is a guy. We also understand what you say.
So everyone's vocabulary is bad like ours.
So we should also speak in such language to the lead.
Can. Ox, oaks will come into it.
Put your finger down, sir. [Laughter]
No one is in tension in 2000.
Hey, in 2000 you had something to do with Potronics.
Will get it.
Why am I talking about another brand?
yes?
You will get some compensation for the damage.
Brother, it will look very dirty here.
[Laughter]
If you are listening to songs with damage on. I think
I want to turn straight after this sound.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation] It's Only Because I To Own It.
ok nice wa nice ok I
I am excited, I just realized it for the first time
Two Sindhis have come to our show once.
or that's true
And this will save us money.
On the first question, brother, this has happened very rarely.
Wow
I'll be back [laughs].
You had two lives, one was yours.
Their game is over on our next correct answer.
It will end here, okay, but you will have a
We will give you the option to lock it when any of your
If the winning amount was on the empty safe
There is no use in locking it. So further
Let's earn you some money whenever you want if
that these two Sindhis want not to earn
You can put a lock on it. Ok?
Now for the same amount one for ₹2000
An alternate question will appear. Hmm, he looks at
We all are. Come on sir.
What kind of student was I in school?
Table
Nady Kit.
Noddy.
Rebel backbencher?
The Sporty Kit.
A teacher's pet. Oh! Definitely not a teacher's stomach.
Was. It does not occur to teachers that the child
Shouldn't be cool.
But she was a teacher's pet earlier, that's why she
Regret is currently coloring her hair.
I don't think teachers have pets because
Brother, I actually do not follow Raunak's theory.
I support.
Haven't spoken yet
She said it right.
Well, it looks like he's a very
Must be a nerdy artist that's very technical
Must be making things. So he did a lot in school
Must have studied religiously. Or
And Now She Is a Reveal Turned
Or sorry, not revel or nadi then
Earlier there was Nadi in the school, now there is Revel
the person who
Yes
I changed my childhood name, that's it
Because that part is no longer what I used to
To be I'm sinking now and in the 10th, a little
applause
There is no power brother, there is no power in the story.
[applause] [cheering] either
Are they happy or are their hands dirty?
[laughter] Something just happened.
too much
Yes.
So either she is a nerdy kid or a teacher
Pet Is What I Think Because Now
Because those who were bullies in school
He sits quietly at the shop.
Isn't it? Correct [laughs].
Correct.
[Appreciation]
So you must have seen its opposite also. Chotu so
Take off your shoes. who was a fool in school
Is. He is humbled in this land. She is humbled
In Land. Is anyone getting their logic in their head?
In? Audience?
Very thick glasses.
Very thick glasses. So she's like
Looking at the Books Close.
Good book is made from many books, glasses book
From. So people tell who this illiterate person is.
Wow, look what a scholarly person has come.
Look at sports, that's why we don't take it
Because sports can be had anywhere.
Nothing else has been established.
She is eating biryani.
Yes. Look at Idar Nadi Gate and Teacher's Pet. I
feel like this a person who believe has a
Value System and Stands for Horror
value system. Right or wrong? value
You define the system.
Value system means that I am not going to
B. Teacher's Pet. I am what I am.
What's the problem with teachers' stomachs?
Hey, go away.
Brother, if you were in school right now [laughs].
I would have called your parents brother. If
If it was Nady then I mean like he also had 9.4
I have told this with so much shame. Isn't it? If
If he had done something good academically
He should have mentioned it somewhere. So far they have
He has highlighted his loyal nature.
Ok?
so and so
All these sycophants are very good.
There is no problem in this
The teachers pack has no values
would not have been
[Cheers]
[Praise] Right Na
You know how useful that is to us [laughs].
Son, go and get the duster, I will do it myself.
I will go
In the class, our little friends and friends
leaving behind
come and eat
[Laughter]
Look, I think he's nerdy. Teacher's Pet
Do either of them, whichever is right for you.
It seems.
Well, let's do one thing at a time because there are many
Is expressive. I will say each option
So react to that. hands down hands down
Put it down.
Well, I won't get this life again.
was not that
Girlfriend and then she had such a nose in her face
O!
Oh, this is what he does.
Let's see who reacts best. Correct
Is? Ok ok. I will tell you four options.
you see it. I see it. and between
I put a split screen on both of them.
Will post a reaction.
Ok. Put your hands down.
Nicet
[applause][laughter] I think theirs
It's done in inner wear.
Pacha [applause] Pacha and Pacha [laughter]
Free purchase is fine. Rebel Bag Bencher
The Sporty Kid
[Laughter]
You just keep blowing air like this.
You don't look free from all cosmetic surgery.
yes. [Laughter]
Before Photo A Teacher's Pet
This is the teacher's pet. Trying to Play School
Or trying to play school.
Ok. What did you do teachers? [Laughter]
This is not the swag you have
There must have been someone among you, never.
Sometimes on teachers. Brother, have you ever been to school?
You haven't gone. This boy did not go to school
Is. This boy has gone to school and she will come soon.
Will happen. Isn't it? who go outside the school
By doing this on the bike. [Laughter]
Are you paying teachers? Why don't you hand
Are you picking it up? When asking. [Laughter]
[Praise] Sir, you are actually asking something.
I was very drunk but she didn't
Don't suppress your expression by saying it a little bit
I tried to bet on teachers. someone
Saw it here
Or you have been watching it since then.
Look, it is either of these two. Correct
Is. Let's take a risk and see
Because the last one was done right, so it doesn't matter.
No.
Let's lock D and Abe for 20,000 right? Yes
Let's Lock a Teacher's Pet
If something goes wrong, you won't be sad either.
Ok
If 2000 are gone, you will not be sad, then one
Tell me the expression and I'll make it [laughs]
So that means we also have a cough, okay, that's it.
I have to do it as it comes [laughs].
what is it what is it what is the answer you
what are you
If we had done it right, it would
Wouldn't you just go away
Yes
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]. There's a sequel to Bacup [laughs].
Okay all right. No problem. Won ₹2,000
Is. You want to lock ₹20,000?
No.
₹2,000 is a lot.
No. [Laughter]
Put.
No.
Were you offended when you called you a teacher?
stomach?
No, I kind of was. [Laughter]
So we were right?
Kind of the. But you were more nerdy.
Do you want to say this? Ok. Something
No. Ok. She has won ₹20,000. Every question
After this, you will tell me one fact about yourself.
In. Ok. Fact I am friends. My
X borrowed money from me before I found it
Out he cheated on me.
How many rupees
not telling?
You can't even tell the money. Brother, did you understand?
Correct.
Brother, I have lost a huge amount.
Actually, it's one of your old questions.
The answer is also being that they are their parents
I am a little scared of it because this one and
Due to fear of whom she might not want to tell.
Look, protect your ex's respect and do something.
It is not there. The family does not know
Needed
Correct. [sound of clearing throat]
Correct.
Write it, you can write it like this.
Or write this down too.
There must be something in it.
or or
Ok. Ok. Next question. ₹4000
For.
I wrote this sentence.
X was a pony but this one was also a failure.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
House Poet.
What did he do with the money?
Open a biryani shop. [Laughter]
Ped [throat clearing sound] of hiss
Credit card use.
Boat a car.
What?
Went on a boys trip.
Yes. Paid me back in installments.
Vent on Boy Strip.
Brother, look what he does with the money.
Answer paid me back can't it be?
It cannot happen at all.
What this means is that our team
It is not there at all.
Can it be fixed? He asked what did you do?
[Laughter]
Our team doesn't know anything else.
Brother, I have a theory.
Yes.
Please.
His ex took money from him.
Went on a boys trip and realized there that
He has gone.
Oh Oh
on that trip
Yes
So, their money was recovered, right?
Brother, a lot of money was spent on the boat and car.
will be
That's why no one is telling me the money, that's why it's big
There will be money but tell me one thing if someone
If he asks, he will ask in such a way that you give it to him or
Will you say something about me getting the credit?
Deuces of cards to be paid
Yes, look, credit card dues are 100%
It is possible because the answer is very easy but
I think the team must have made it
Went on a Boys Trip can also happen and
Boat A Car I am in these only C and B
In
See Paying Off Credit Card Use Is Like
It's a good thing you can do for your ex.
Yes, yes
Like, it's okay, friend, you
He must not have gossiped about her.
This. Yes
It's either a carrent boy
Brother, it was a big amount.
Yes Boat a Car
Butt Eye
He has taken some money, not because he
I got him a car because he is a DJ.
No money on this
Correct correct, will it hurt you much?
Bye
To me, if any innerwear is for dorms
Apart from
If it pricks, that ball pricks, this is very
soft
I think it's I think it's best because
Boyster would irritate you more he just had fun
How did they reach Indonesia now?
This was on that trip.
[cheering] These are his sides.
we had a great we had a great time with
Your money [laughs].
And with your boyfriend
Logic is coming
Would be weird of if someone goes on a boy's
Trip after taking my money car
You wouldn't be that paid with the car now
Boy Strip Lust
Boys Trip Is
What
Boy strip is havers
So you boy strip with your friends
What are you doing brother, I am just playing tricks.
Are.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
What did you want? Is this a boys trip?
House?
I'm also more into boys trips.
I am inclined.
Let's go then [laughter]
I think let's go?
I am also on a boys trip.
Come on brother.
Let's go boys.
Let's book it.
What is the meaning of hitting the ball?
Wandering. Like this is how one has to drive.
Holding hands like this in the gaadi
[Cheers]
Yes.
Ok. He comes on a voice trip. This way
Will keep doing this until they lock the correct answer
May it not come.
Oye, okay. Lock it brother. What are you doing?
yes? Why are you doing this? [Laughter]
You have taken your own money.
Oh no oh no because she is doing it.
I think she is celebrating she
Celebrating and it's not bot's.
Oh [ __ ].
What are we celebrating wrongly?
Answer?
Because while we were doing this, he also did that
Did. Which means she is celebrating it.
It's good that we are the wrong lovers
I haven't even explained this show that much, friend.
Well, this happiness can't be anything, basically.
No
reverse [laughs] it let's
She can't be happy
boat a car let's just go with it man okay
You give him 4000 rupees, right? [laughs]
Okay, he's taking the lead for the first time, bot.
Then you would have done it on a car
Yeah, I'm taking OAKS, man [laughs].
Baby's ox baby don't you remember that these
How does the oak tree give
You're saying this [laughs]. You are saying this
yes. Yes, okay. So let's go boys trip
[Laughter]
I am getting stuck only on the amount.
Bot a car requires a lot of money, man.
Boys go on trips, but Raunak said that
I am taking charge. bot a car do
Are.
Boys trip, man. [Laughter]
Brother, tell me. Ok. Ok. For now
Let's take a boy trip.
Yes for now. At present
What is it right now? Then this will remain. come back
Go.
Let's Lock Sea Boys Tray
She is laughing a little as if she is laughing at me.
Has been.
No, I just keep laughing.
Isn't it? Because there is no work [laughs].
I keep having fun.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. It is locked
No?
Hey brother, it's okay. Sorry.
Brother, throw your brick and hit the next person.
Day. Okay, let's go okay. Let's Reveal the Answer
Please. Because four have won.
Please forgive me
Raunak I am so sorry. you hit my dick
You can do this brother. I am so
Sorry. Did you pay the full amount for the car?
No. No.
Okay car, yes how much money did you pay?
Not completely.
50%
A few lakhs.
A few lakhs? Friend, I have become such a prisoner.
I need it friend.
We all need it. Right, such a thing is not lakh?
50% 20%
Episode 1 Point Baad Tera Bachcha Bada
I will see what happens. [Laughter]
When I was born, my father was saying this
If we also get prisoners.
Well, tell me, is it above 50% or 50%?
This is not even mentioned below.
Down to the low 50s.
And it's good whether we get that money back or not.
meet?
No.
What? [Laughter]
Well, whose money was that?
Whose money was that?
Hey, I mean he took it after saying something else. Bus
Then
Ok. You have won ₹4,000. lock you up
Is.
No.
What is this? Friend, it's okay, no problem.
There is no worry about money.
There is no worry about money. This
It's a game, I will play it.
It's a game, I'll play it.
That's what our boyfriend said.
True based on two [laughs] stories.
Okay next fact please.
Every Time I Go Through a Major Heart
Break. I changed my hair color.
Absolutely not because I
Asked. We
I told him sir, the fact is true.
There is an attack
[Laughter]
So
I said this
Brother, you will understand this completely at the end of the show.
I will say from Mumbai, brother, now I want a clip.
I'll do a clip next time.
We lost because, well, well, well [laughs].
ok cool plus it says every time
I mean, it happened a lot of times
which is the best color
I think I've done red a lot
Red a lot and you didn't even finish it completely.
So this was only half the color I had, what is the
What are the colors you used?
Purple, Blue, Green.
Green? You need a lot of confidence, friend Green.
By taking hair.
Someone will say that Dhaniya has arrived.
It takes a lot of confidence brother.
That AI coriander. I am coriander.
Ok. Next question.
You want to play quickly, right?
Yes.
Play fast, friend.
Ok. Let's play quickly. Eth
Give me your hand. Aye [laughs]
Brother, if you have a breakup, what value will you give?
Will you apply it?
Oh man, that means [laughs].
In your beard.
Next question.
Which habit of mine will drive my roommate crazy?
Dhaniya came again. [Laughter]
Playing the same song on repeat.
Keep the AC on all here.
Loud video call conversation.
Not keeping my room tidy. Ok.
Brother, A and C are also very correct answers.
And we can also be deceived in a big way.
Can. So tell me what I think.
It could be A or it could be B.
Keeping the AC on all year because anyway
She must be burning with anger that whoever comes
He cheats. Do AC at 18. something like
Maybe you do.
And this color of hair it stage better when
It's a cool room.
Oye no no. Hair is black
I'm saying anything, man.
Yes. Black absorbs the most heat.
He does, right? So it stays cold
Absolutely. 10
Its colours keep changing. like now
It has halved it so it is at 22.
[Laughter]
As soon as it is completed, it goes away. [Laughter]
And as soon as he becomes black, he is 35.
A or D?
A or B?
Yes, I also have a thing for D.
Inclination? Because
That is yours
[Laughter]
You told me the boy strip was full of air
Is. Inclination towards D
When we went to the boystrip and locked the D in that
They climb on it. [Laughter]
[Cheers]
But having said that?
Yes
Life Line
There is also a lifeline. Okay, thank you brother.
[laughter] We even have a lifeline.
Do we have a lifeline?
Very good brother, you have given very good clarity of
There is mind. Applause for the brother.
[applause] [cheering voice]
I give you one from Damage
Reward. Redeem it at dimensions.com
You take it. Brother, we have a lifeline too.
Is.
No no, are you mad? 25 75
Totally different.
So let's see, we know that all of us
It seems so. So remove one.
Ok. Let's use it.
Well I thought one would remain.
[Laughter]
Brother, whose side have you come from? understand me
Did not come. From the side of science. [Laughter]
Let's use lifeline 2575 see what 75
activated
I will remove this, see this loud sisterfucker
Video call conversation which we are sure that
No, brother, you were very rude [laughs], friend.
These we
You gave them a suggestion, right?
oh [ __ ] man
[Laughter]
Brother
But we are already stuck on playing on the same
Song or not keeping it depends on the
Song If You Are Playing Sukhbir On Repeat
ok play it but not keeping my room time
Rotary AM is playing songs that are good
Morning Good Morning Good Morning
So it can be a little irritating.
Brother, this is much better biryani than Swiggy
made and so on
Second did you think Rodeo AM has good
Morning Songs Because They What Am
[Laughter]
and what good morning good night
Riggo PM Hus Good Night Good Night Good
Night or good I'm not keeping my room
tidy take me what is i office
I will go to Bombay
[Laughter]
Now Didi, I am also feeling like it, okay let's
Locked and not keeping my room tight
This guy laughed last time when we
My ass was torn apart [laughs]
Same thing that's been happening for the last half an hour.
So you know, that's what they do [laughs].
Dude, that Amitabh Bachchan
I said I was playing the same song on
repeat
I don't know that yet either
that's true
What is the answer? If this happens then you will give me some relief.
I said I said keeping the AC
On.
Brother, you read all four options. Because of this
All those things that come out of your mouth.
You [laughs] put on the edit what I did before
I had said.
Ok. You have won ₹8,000. Congratulations to you.
It was not even close at all.
If I don't lock it.
Won't you apply it?
Won't you apply it? Why are you taking the risk?
Just like that.
Or go for it. Go for it. to be like this
Needed
Just see, she will go laughing.
Ok. Ok. Next fact please.
If I Had to Describe My Music. I
Call it uplifting music for sad people.
I as opposed to down lifting music
For happy people. [Laughter]
good Morning Good Morning.
Can you give an example of a song?
900 Miles Karke is a song by house music.
How much will this cost in kilometers? [Laughter]
[Applause] Don't be sad, man. Yes. So,
What do you do with it? That's what the song in it
that I am 900 away from 900 miles away
From my home but it's like a very
Uplifting song like You Should Play It.
Okay all right. Next question.
What feels like a tax of my life?
Your music?
[Laughter]
Having introverted friends?
No, no, he himself is an introvert.
Being in the Wrong Place at the Wrong Time?
Like the show.
Not Having Generational Wealth?
Absolutely.
Whenever I book a cab, Wagon R arrives.
Is.
Brother, whenever I book a car, Wagon R comes.
She goes. It's my team's way of bringing humor.
It is a try.
And she doesn't look like much either.
That brand conscious that why this Wagon R
Has been. I got some premium Ubergo
Get a deal of Rs. It doesn't look like that.
Being in the Wrong Place at the Wrong Time.
100%
Because this is sad. by cheating
This is my personal belief. As much as we thought
Yes, we have defecated. Or let's just be straight.
Or is it straight B? Are? Locket, locket, locket,
Locket, locket, locket, not open to discussion.
Lock it, B.
Let's Locke Up Being in the Wrong Place.
Don't we all relate with this at this moment
In time.
In Hindi.
What do you like?
Ok. Just do it. Just reveal it.
This time she is not laughing.
Oh yes.
I am sad. There is sadness in his eyes.
Oh ho, fake laughter.
So book its Wagon R.
I feel it's time to go. Lock
So he did not do it.
Reveal it.
she go
She will be seen going.
Now she will be seen leaving with perfectly shaped hair.
with.
Etc. etc. Not your beats [laughs].
Let's see brother. What are uplifting beats?
These? For sad people. Dupchik dish. tell me
Brother. [music]
Fired.
When will it happen? Oho
[applause][music]
wrong place wrong time
But do you know what the real thing is? For yourself
One can listen to uplifting music.
[laughter] 900 Miles From Here. O dear
Applause once for four. thank you so
Mach. True [praise] A great player, man.
It's a great player. tell something.
Thank you. Listen, let people know where they can
Follow You and Find Your Music.
Sinkora
It's Sing Kora Music on Instagram on
Spotify Everywhere.
Once for him [praise] well he
By the way, if it had locked it then its
You would have the option to play all on nothing. But
It has gone to zero. So then these
Will have to go.
Oh, one more round of applause. Thank you so much
For coming. very nice. [Appreciation]
Very good. B bye. Thank you.
Ok. Ok. Do you have any comedy?
I have heard gossip which you can verify from us now.
Do you want to know if this is true or something?
Yes, ask, ask. Ask me.
Brother, I will tell you.
Yes you are completely right about that gossip.
I tell you, they are doing well, they are doing well
Is.
Yesterday one na tomorrow one na podcast I told you
I had told you. There's a podcast. he saw someone
Have you seen it? I am not laughing in that
It is on this matter. I tell you this because
Not by fighting. So there is no caster inside it.
And there's a person in front who probably knows why
It is from the community. Perhaps he claims so
Because I saw the whole thing, I knew.
No. So inside him he is saying that you
Do you know someone famous?
to someone you know who cheats and
He said that he is a comedian.
[Laughter]
And he has millions of subscribers.
And I know that she has
Have sex together. And he also gives her this
He says that if you do it with your wife
I will see and so on. He is saying all this
And everyone in the comments is Solanki.
It is clear Solanki. I want to tag him.
One is saying Solanki Bhai either you are mine
You are my brother. Or you are being rude.
Brother, I had to comment on that.
Why are you tagging me? people me
They are sending it because they got caught.
So if you are not there then who is there? See if you
Won't you tell these people who you are? donation
Everybody Will Assume It's Him. Or [laughter]
I don't see people doing it.
No.
I have no idea.
Who what is the correct person that?
Given that all three of us are married.
Right?
It could be one of the three of us.
Both of us have millions of followers.
Needed
We don't have subscribers.
I am the only one, then what else? [Laughter]
What can we do? Now this is the last time when
I will tell everyone ok guys. [Laughter]
Okay, let's get started?
[cheering] Okay. Let's
Start the Miss Presence That If We Can
Guys.
[Appreciation]
Let's call our today's contestant.
Her name is Anushka Sharma.
[Cheers]
from London
Anushka is 22 years old. oh well for now
Studying Masters in Fashion Styling
Have been. Anushka is very impulsive in life
Takes decisions. But the surprising thing is that
It is that most of the times they survive.
Let me tell you some facts about Anushka.
Should I give it? Add asafoetida to the food
I don't like it at all. What do I do with this
What about the matter? What do you keep asking all this?
He doesn't like the asafoetida seasoning [laughs]
Just like watching cricket
I don't like it at all.
Defeat Anushka
Who doesn't like it? All that to him. If Anushka
If she wins ₹50,000 from the show today, then she
I would like to take a course to become a chef with the money.
So leave the masters course in fashion that you are doing.
Will give. Actually, temper it without asafoetida.
I have some [laughs].
We have to make it bigger than that. Ok. call them
Starting Welcome Anushka
[Encouraging voice] Sharma
Anushka Anushka.
Yes, I don't have any strategy today. I
I have just arrived. If I had won, I would have won.
If I don't win [music], it's still OK.
I feel my appearance. Like that, I am very
I look cute. But I am not you
No. With the money I think I'll be going
Ahead and Learning a Cutlery [Music] Course
Or only the admission fee has come and it is done, do the rest.
will take
Anushka Anushka Anushka Anushka
Chef Anushka Chef Anushka
Hi, applause please for applause
[applause] [cheering voice]
Oh, you are tired, if you were playing cricket then
doesn't get tired
So you don't get tired, what are you, this is in the beginning
arrogantly
What the hell does this thing belong to?
Oh no, those Anushka Sharma jokes
That's why you keep listening very frequently
I got irritated.
I judged the first one correctly.
OK [laughs]
slit ass
He says anything. Ok. Anushka today
The most materialistic purchase till date
What have you done?
me too on clothes
What is the most expensive?
What was the most expensive thing you bought?
Meaning I did more shopping once
A little.
How many had it been?
I will not tell this.
Meaning whether you are arrogant or not. The question is next
Go. You feel guilty.
Maybe that could be the question. Ok, good. Correct
Is. He had bought some clothes, so you
these questions
Right.
I asked.
He had asked this.
Sorry.
You asked this question [laughter].
Ok.
I get up status of yes. Let's go.
English or English.
I have come from outside.
Ask questions.
Anushka Sharma: What was the best year of your life?
Life? And what did you do that year?
Its total has become 22.
[laughter] [throat clearing sound]
I feel 2020 mein bhi ai mean main 12th ka
You didn't have to give the paper, right? In 2021. O!
ok best life
I am bad in studies. I am bad. paper
I did not have to give it.
No, we did not have to give the paper.
Percentage
No, how did you come?
Ah, he did something about 11th and 10th.
Gave.
No, by doing anything
Yes, that means he had calculated the average.
How many came in 10th then? ok my question
It will not count. I'm just asking this
Am. If you want to tell me, then tell me.
No, I will not tell you again.
So let me count the questions. How many came?
In 12th?
No comments. Well tell me the truth, next question is
What?
I will not tell. I will not tell it like this.
Okay okay, fine.
[Laughter]
Do we already know this? I am not
Should I tell you? This is a little bit bubbly.
Do you know what happened now? She is 22 years old
Is. His dreams have not been shattered yet.
So your marriage has become a waste. This is lost
If your dreams are fulfilled then.
Hey, you're over 30. [Laughter]
Haven't you heard the latest gossip?
What about it?
Which one?
[Laughter]
You will have to tell this back to me Anushka.
I like everything. [Laughter]
Ok. Ok. I have my question. Such
What is the mistake in your life that you are making?
Do you regret it?
Masters?
Shouldn't have done Masters.
Are you doing a job? Masters?
You are doing Masters in Fashion Styling
yes. do not do do do do do do
should should should do do do.
I feel that I could have gone ahead and done a
Internship and done a job. It would have been.
Nothing has happened with it yet.
Make it the worst like monsters [laughs]
Took. Ask him if he has any jobs.
Not there. That is their mistake.
Masters will say, you had said abroad, right?
Karma is doing the masters.
Dude, he said abroad.
Abrabod.
Which country is that bro? [Laughter]
Let's move ahead.
Your question. You've got to be in Bollywood [laughs].
Since you are a fashion student, you should try Bollywood
Who has the best fashion sense among all?
Does it feel good?
that you relate to
No not related but I feel it is a good design.
No relate you want no relate.
Diljit Diljit you know. What will I know if
You like Diljit from Fashion?
You Know
Relate.
Anushka Sharma fashion.
Anushka Sharma.
Ok. So I have a question. Yours
Both are done, right? I have one left. You and
Your friend group. You people meet people
If you judge, then on what basis?
Do you judge?
Fashion sense.
Tell me how are we doing now?
Don't waste this question. Brother, our
Life is being wasted. [laughter] if
If we are bad then we will get 10 paise marks.
Keep giving to all three. And then tell me the reason.
Well, do one thing, upgrade our
In that.
At?
How much is Ashish?
At? ET [laughs] I did my best today ET
Okay, he came with number two stylist.
came for him [laughs]
Or you're a stylist that's not tasteful
Unfair Advantage You're a Stylist
No You Are You Will Get 10
we both got 10 we both got ya
Sisterfucker, five by five
[Laughter]
I am Punch and he is Punch
Okay, the questions are done and we understand.
It is said that we do not know anything.
Ok.
Ok. Ok.
All these questions have been raised.
All the questions are answered.
O friend
This one too, why are we doing this? They
All the questions are answered. Ok. So once I
Let Domesh call it out.
Ok.
Guys, thank you so much to Damens Joe
Those who have supported us.
[Cheers]
Yes.
Yes. [Praise] The Most Comfortable Inner
Ware Brand For Man.
That's true I ya.
Most comfortable.
Or you just made me wear it. I love it.
[Laughter]
He is my stylist.
These
Ok. OK let's get started this show is cool.
First Question on Dermens Presents
Again.
What is something my parents still don't
No off.
Option A that I hit my results in class
11th.
Option B is that I drink their alcohol.
There's alcohol.
Option C that I crash their car. Hmm.
Option D, That I Regularly Stolen Money
From them.
Brother, has this peak come here? this is
All these are criminal activities, friend. And here
But she was judging us.
Anushka Sharma, I have
Our style is bad but our people are fine.
Yes, brother, I regularly steal money. Regularly.
Either they have so much money that they know
It is not working.
Look, I think it can't be
Regularly stole money. Yes.
Because it is not his job. If her parents
Find out then she can't steal money any more.
Not brother. I think he's fairly rich
background because he studied Arod
Abroad or where is it written Abroad? you did not
I said London.
I said, I am Anushka Sharma speaking.
Was.
Oh London oh [ __ ].
Have you been thinking this since then?
Yes, these masters are studying in fashion outside.
Are.
No, this is what you are reading.
Yes. So, has she come from outside to do this?
[Laughter]
Then again, it could be anything.
He is rich. Are you rich?
From
Look, if she were not rich, she would have
Oh, where is it, sir [laughs].
gets scattered
Those who were unlucky would start saying all this.
It's okay, there's dal roti, she talks.
Correct Correct
Hey, if the car crashes, you will know about it.
Okay, but you can use any such name, right?
Can't put the name or hit the car
And she got it repaired and came back with her
One thing she also said in the intro was that I
Get into trouble, but some how I get out of it
When I come, she took an impulsive decision.
I will give you a race, why did you become a sisterfucker?
Look what happened, the money was stolen.
No urgency is established
I am drinking alcohol little by little, there is no point in it.
Urgency established but emulsive I
I thought I would take out the car and hit it today itself.
I give it some
This is also something to hide
This is something to hide
Correct yes crash their car
crash their car
Crash Their Car Crash Their Car Let's Lock
C Crash Their Car If You Were Us
So what would you suck? [Laughter]
No, what if you were in your place?
Do you suck? With you
Crash their car. How?
O!
That means we are going home. Are going.
I did it to you.
She's a reverse psychologist.
He doesn't know that much.
Hey, I went to such a clinic. He is like this
She's sitting [laughs].
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Oh my God.
Oh my God. Oh, brother [laughs].
Are you okay? How did this come to your mind?
Buddy? It was too good, friend. In my thought
From Domens to you
[Cheers]
A decision should be given. [Appreciation]
What if there's something arrogant about it, friend? These
Are you looking at it like that? Do it. [Laughter]
There is some money inside it.
Ok. Tell me brother. Tell me the correct answer.
Reveal it.
Just make it green, man.
Come on man.
Just Green It. [Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Wow, cool, okay, so in your first question.
We have caught you. Oh, it didn't hurt. Brother
He is rich.
Yes.
Well, what will we do from here? chef becoming a chef
Only rich people do this course.
He has all these problems too. Asafoetida This
It's so middle class, man. This asafoetida tadka
etc.
What is this tadka? Yes. These in the baffles
Can it happen? A little pancake type
This is a girl.
Isso fart?
What?
Esoferty. That's what Hinge is. you guys
Who doesn't know? ESO4 [laughs]
Brother, we are working people
Baby I buy ESO fruit from my car
Am. [Laughter]
Be quiet.
Till now because we judge our contestants
They do it and you people keep watching like that
You guys are being very judgmental. I
I want to give you a chance where
You guys will judge things. be ready for it
For?
Nice nice.
Lovelace.
This segment is from Damage.
Coming to you friends. Let there be applause
Go for the damage once.
[Cheers]
Let there be applause.
Okay, now I'm going to ask you some questions.
We will give it to the person who gives the correct answer.
Dominance currency of ₹2100
Which you can redeem from dms.com. Correct
Is? First question? But first we pick this up
Who will answer? There is a couple.
Guys a couple?
Or OK.
Ok. Ok. Did you have a love marriage?
How are you doing?
doing fine.
And can do better. Ok. One question.
Are you guys ready? What is your name?
Chase.
What? Chase?
[Laughter]
What is your name? Chase?
Just.
Just just.
Just it.
And Her Name Is Chin.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Ok. first question. Let me state the facts first
That the west of Damensh gives your body 2°
Keep a cooler. The question is which one am I
Anger in situations that get 2 degrees warmer
Am? I have a question about me. A. When someone
The relative says, come on, tell me a joke.
B When someone asks when the next season of Rose is coming
Is? C When someone meets and says big fan
Akash Gupta brother.
Or when people talk as soon as they post a video
You forgot your YouTube password, you dog.
C [throat clearing sound]
See I don't think it will be See because why
would you be upset a someone called you by your
Name
It's 4 degrees hotter, man [laughs].
At least color your hair green.
ok karunesh bro
[Laughter]
Let's Lock C Can We Lock C Reveal the Answer.
Do whatever you can.
Okay, okay [laughter] it said you have
There is an answer.
Okay, okay, one minute, one minute. One minute,
One minute. Solanki, Solanki Before You Read The
Answer that's written by your team. what really
Out of these four things? Annois U. But
There is no answer here. Well, you are yours
The answer is in your heart.
It comes to my heart.
You have to go to a reverse psychologist.
[Appreciation]
I get most angry when
Someone says, did you hear the joke?
I go to Kilas.
[Laughter]
You seem very comfortable to me. These
I get it from Damage.
[Cheers]
Damage currency.
Is it really great brother? 2
X Softer. You know?
2 x?
2 x Soft.
Oh, minus only one x.
That is it. 1x is the same. [Laughter]
2 x Softener.
That's crazy.
What can you do for double soft underwear?
Can you in life?
I can pay triple X. which is
There is no need to do this because the damage will
Already and so affordable.
Yes. [Cheers]
On top of that we cause damage. brother to me
Tears will come. [Laughter]
Very good. One round of applause for brother
Buddy.
amazing. [Cheers]
Applause, friend. Come on man, give it back man. Brother
And absorb tears, water and water also.
Takes. What all?
Absorbs water.
Brother their absorbability oh my
You can cry completely about your inner self like this.
[Laughter]
Everything will be in tears. But I took it off
When I cry, others laugh. [Laughter]
Ok. For the second question, we
People have to be picked up. You pick it up. Any
Tell me the criteria.
Who are a CA is here? anybody who's a ca or
A lawyer?
Which person?
CA CA CA. CA Okay, okay. CA brother
I have a question for you. The fact is that I
It has been found that according to the global average
Men's underwear changes every 6 to 12 months
Are. The question in the world of men is that
What is this average in India? A 30 Days
[Laughter]
The meaning changes
[sound of clearing throat] Let's buy a new one.
Understand? B [laughs]
30 months.
C 30 weeks,
D 300 weeks or this lamp wala that I am
I don't wear it at all. You tell me which 30 months
People change in India. 30 months
2nd year, its correct answer is in 30 months.
Make Some Nice for This Guy. do you get
Damen currency ₹2,100 please from Damensh
Give it to them. Now you will be able to change instantly.
Yes and change it.
This will last you for 2 years easily. How
long is
So this is a lot.
How Long Is It Done Bro? This is the last.
I only heard how long I said
Why are you asking, friend? ok but now I
So friends, let's play the game further.
To.
Huh [cheering voice]
[Applause] Let the questions come, please. For the Same
Amount.
It is still only ₹2 thousand.
What is the worst email I've ever received?
Received.
You are selected for? If [laughter] you can.
[Cheers]
No, no, please don't send this to them by email.
Give.
Option A, a five-page long document
From my ex breaking up with me.
Five pages long.
Option B, A Request for My Feedbacks.
Option C, The Prince of Sudan offering me 5
Ten million.
No, not this.
Option D, a major proposal by a 40-year-old
Old man.
Brother [laughs] and he is here today
He is here brother, how did you change your email?
Why does his friend send a marriage proposal through mail?
will send
No, 40 years old
No, a 40 year old man, of course.
You can send it if you want to write something long.
Look at my Excel, these are attachments.
Sheets mine [laughs]
So brother, I have a logic, I am the last
I would like to submit it, please do it now, yes this
Have access to email, okay, some 40 year old
Man is stocking, this is weird isn't it?
Where can I get email from? Instagram
Pay if some influencer type work like this
If you don't do this, the email will not be visible.
Email
Look him in the eye and say it.
Brother, then I will become a 40 year old man.
Buddy.
[laughter] I have this diagonal in each eye.
I talk after looking at the diagonal. Ok?
To college professors.
College Professor: Yes, that was logic too. But
The professor should propose for marriage.
This is a big leap, friend. and this
And this is not weird, this is weird.
ok i sent the same
This isn't weird, what could possibly happen?
college professor speaking college professor
You are talking like this, become my grandmother
I will make you pass Tenu [laughter]
Brother, I think we should know about the world.
Must be that ape man is everywhere
[screaming]
Here it is
Identified Himself Thank You For
Identification Police
Oye Oye my father has come.
Do one thing. One of his lives is gone.
Take the lifeline now.
The game will be over completely.
I will send you back to Mumbai right now.
What is in it?
Okay, okay, lifeline, lifeline.
Lifeline 25-75 Activate Right Now.
Don't suggest anything right now. [Laughter]
He has said that he will remove the Sudanese one now.
See.
Why did I say this after turning off the mic?
spoke? [Laughter]
You stop paying these people their salaries if
They remove Sudan.
[Laughter]
They are saying what salaries
They don't get any salary
I think I only give termination currency
They are hungry but they have innerwear.
That's great [laughs].
Brother, tell me what to do now.
Now you are trapped
You tell me now, you tell me well
Ma'am numbers hold
It is not even given in comparison to this, so you
Can you tell me friend, I haven't even passed 12th.
in a manner
Bachelor to Kari
No, no, she is arguing too much. This is very
She is arguing.
If it were an old uncle, he would be angry.
Go. [Laughter]
Daughter, you give very strange answers.
daughter
I think I think that because she said to me it could
Just be a five page long document for her
X.
It Makes Sense for Her. because he
Relationship.
Yeah.
Because he must have been hurt by the breakup. and him
Then I will not say that
You hit the car, right? What to do?
Yes, I hit the car, okay I will tell you. my one
There is logic. Who has raised your hand? You
Keep your hands up until then. And put both of them up.
What is the question?
Keep both hands up and then we will be damaged from above.
I will bring it to you.
Listen Listen.
And he will go away because he is so soft.
It is fabric. Applause, friend.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Yes, I am saying that this is not the question.
What was the weirdest thing that happened? Question
Not what's the weirdest email you've received?
So I can tell someone who is closest to you.
What's that weird email? And you have
Such an amazing story that a 40 year old man
I found the marriage proposal tricky.
I have it.
I'm like this earlier or I had said which one
The idiot will attach the document.
But that is weird. So She Must Be Telling
Her Friends How Weird That My Ex Roter
On a word dog and then attached it.
Yes, so right now you were on D.
No, no, no.
I want a no. Yes brother, this is not D.
How come there are two idiots here?
A document guy [laughs].
And I, the one who trusted you
[cheering voice] over and over and over again
This man turns around, he looks like A, he looks like B.
It seems like it will say edit again.
Brother, tell me what I said correctly.
Said Raunak is a genius [laughs] boyfriend
gonna have to
do boyfriend
boyfriend
Let's go ordering boyfriend a gum
make me your boyfriend
boyfriend
Let's move ahead brother. This is the first question.
Let's do A A.
Let's lock a five page long
Documents from my ex breaking up
With me.
That is that is pretty weird bro.
That's Beard Bro. Right now the first
I have a question, friend.
Can I tell you something? I can look at
The Entire Audience and The Entire Audience Is
Still having a lot of fun. Dispite How
Long the Show Has Been? But how Anushka is so
Fun. Board Right Now?
There is nothing like that, right?
No. Ok. [laughs] His video gives a
Shid. ok don't worry we will help you a lot
I am going to free you soon. [Laughter]
Now live sorry
I told you.
Ok, good. I apologize if it happened
I will ask.
[Cheers]
With whom? With whom?
Apologies to all the girls who told us
They ask for it. All three of you said T, right?
All the boys said sorry.
All the women you.
Well, okay. Ok. You have won ₹2000.
Congratulations to you.
₹2000 congratulations.
How are you doing? God is looking up.
[Laughter]
My days have changed.
Covid and today. You know the rest in 206.
Unnecessary eye roll yes. Just Like Whatever
2000 DU.
Same same, same, same. Okay, okay, next
Facts please. I was once an Eve T police man.
Oh Papa, hey my father is a policeman
The policeman is not my father.
What is this brother?
Not every policeman has a father.
No, brother. People like this, police is your father
[Laughter]
Policeman, this is so wrong.
Some action has happened again. you said something
Some?
gone.
Sad sad.
I will talk to Papa.
Ok. Questions please.
O dear
Which of the professions have I not been if
T bye [laughs]
First option my father
Option A Lawyer
Loire
Option B: Doctor
No problem but doctors
Option C Software
Software 100% No
Option D Cab Driver
Hello Hello, you are doing well
Option
Graphic designer too
One second, one second, let's start with one
Thing.
What the [ __ ] is Happening?
So he also doesn't know whether he knows or not.
There is at profession there are two doctors.
I think it's Doctor A and Doctor B.
A singer is attendant.
Sorry.
A singer one is attendance.
So he will not be a doctor.
Hey, she is joking brother.
D
Hmm! Hmm hmm
Brother, just wait a second and tell us on what basis?
This is because in this we are such that these people
It can be like this, yes, and then those people
This is how we got into the mindset, okay one second.
one second one second
But you two
All of them are capable of
Evening Teasing Which Is Completely Wrong | who is
The Most Likely Let's Suck That Because I
Think this is a trick question where am I
We Think Is the Most Likely Will Not Be the
Correct Answer |
That's the game
[Laughter]
So you control your production team.
Yaar Ye Art Art
Let's do one thing and see what it means
People of which profession will be affected the most?
That they bring it to the same access thing
Cab drivers sometimes tease me too.
[laughs]
Correct
Do you want 50-50 if you give eight options?
So after doing 50-50 we come back to four.
will go
So 100% I want 50-50
I would prefer a crack jack [laughs].
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Tell me brother, we have to take 50-50 in this.
[Laughter]
What have you done to us? You gave us
Flew the marathon and then got a cab.
See
Brother, I have a doubt. Ok.
Sir yes.
From Lawyer and Software Engineer
There might be less connection.
Why would it be lying there? Yes, because the car
I don't even know that he hit me. to someone
In some cases nothing has happened.
A person has to meet a doctor. cab
The person has to meet the driver.
She is too young to meet a lawyer like this
Randomly. Where can I even ask a software engineer?
Will I get this?
Butt Software
One, there is a software engineer everywhere.
see you.
Yes. And
There's one software engineer here.
Are?
What are you doing all this [laughter]?
[cheering voice] Wrong.
You are also a software engineer.
I mean, I did engineering and
What are you doing friend? You will be a lawyer, right?
Then.
But I have done lawyer law. Losses
And I sometimes run Cap. [Laughter]
The brother is either A or C because the doctor
And can I meet the cab driver sometime?
Or I am also feeling the same as A and C.
Look Sir, I think it must be lawyer only.
Because she is less likely to meet a lawyer
Considering every
But oh yes. So you must not have met the lawyer, right?
You might not have found it. I did not do it. And Lauer in his
Meaning that at least he will be aware of the law.
Brother, I should not do this.
If you don't do it, I will be caught.
But anyway, the [ __ ] police should also be aware.
Needed [Laughter]
Why do you look at me and say that?
Meaning Noise Noise
I think the police should be aware
Needed
Yes.
They also feel the same.
Or okay. Then lawyer, don't you think so?
Yes sir.
You want to say something.
Very common in lawyers
This is very common among lawyers.
You lawyer, put the second camera on this. This
I have said it. Ma'am, you are a lawyer. you are a lawyer
so you are ok
These people had told us earlier also to do D
We did not do it for the previous ones
In the question. Well, we were wrong.
Or okay, one moment, listen to the lawyer saying it himself.
Hey, listen to me.
Ma'am which one do you think it is?
Yes ma'am. Lawyer You Think You Are
Ma'am what about you? Lawyer?
Loire
I go the wee woo women. we made a mistake
Not Listening to the Women. Let's list to the
Women This Time.
Lock the lawyer.
[Laughter]
His mouse moving, I saw you here.
Pay?
There is a guy sitting there like this. [Laughter]
I am sure. look into my eyes
I am sure.
Let's do it.
[Cheers]
[Applause] You survived today, sir. As a lawyer.
one second does this mean that today we
Both have been sent to zero.
[Cheers]
What did you say? What did Sindhi brothers say?
did?
What did you say?
Sindhi brother, scold the destruction.
One second [laughs] applause Anushka
For. Thank you so much.
And well done to him. [Cheers]
If nothing else [praise] we give you Domesh
From the side of hey, I have to take this back crazy girl
Give. [laughter] Carrie, come over to your side. it
It is not for you, without any love words
So you have to speak like this. Yes, okay. Ok.
If nothing else, then for one of your love words,
From Ramesh, Baba for your good luck
Applause please. Thank you so much.
[Cheers]
[praise] If you react like this, I
How will I keep it?
again
Let's do it again once. Brother, we all
There are actors. Ok? Anushka in the full show
You can do DL like this if you ever do this
You should not accept it. [Laughter]
When he turns towards you, you leave the envelope like this,
Hit me with your hands. and revenge on me
Take it out. To you
Anushka, just take it, just take it.
Okay, one second. hold on hold on.
Make some nice for Anushka friend. thank you so
Much for coming. [Cheers]
We will give you something more from Damage.
I want one word. [laughter] What is this?
[Appreciation]
Thank you so much thank you guys. thank you thank you
You. [cheering] Thanks for
Run Kajwani Chirag Pajwani. Thank you so much
For coming. A lot by take care. [Appreciation]
And do visit.com. Thank you so much
Supporting us. Make some nice for Damen
[Cheers]
See you. Bye take care. How are you?
Is? I got angry.
I think how much more than 20,000 we
I know him more.
₹1,000
The ₹1,000 question [laughs]
[music]
He puts any ad on Veet. Xi brother
It is very little. Two [music] Three School I Am
Wearing the match.
I can see beyond the damage.
It can be heard. There has been good lyrics [music].
Home damage inner wear should be heard.
There's a lot of it now, but it
This is what it was
[music]
Which one did you do? How did you like it?
I want Damage's panties.
Because Damage Guys so great. Because I
Get to Mean Judgmental People for the First
Time in my life. I am there. I am not
A judgmental person at.
But Anushka is so bored.
What an episode for We Women
Empowerment. that we gave two girls to one
Did not let me win the money. [laughter] Our today
The takeaway is that being way good at the game
he is bad
It ends quickly.
Once the drowning is over, we will talk again.
[Laughter]